5hourenergy.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - 5-hour ENERGY®

### **EFFECTIVE DATE: February 16, 2017**

Any information that you provide of a confidential personal nature or otherwise through this website (“Site”) will be handled in accordance with the following Privacy Policy (“Policy”).  _Your use of the Site is contingent upon your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of this Site as well as the guidelines of this Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, you may not use the Site.  _

_INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE  _

_Active Collection._  You understand and agree that Living Essentials, LLC and its authorized business partners, affiliates, subsidiaries, and agents (collectively, “Living Essentials”, “us” or “we”) may collect, maintain, and process information provided by you, on and through the Site such as your name and email address (“User Submitted Information”). You represent and warrant that you have permission to share any User Submitted Information you elect to provide Living Essentials and that such information is accurate, current, non-misleading, consistent, and relevant for the purpose for which you are providing information. We may use your User Submitted Information to communicate with you regarding our products and services and those of our subsidiaries, affiliates, and parent companies and any of their related businesses. You may elect to opt-out from receiving materials from us by following the instructions found below in the Opt-Out section.

_Passive Collection._  We may record and collect information about how you use the Site. This data may include your domain name, language, type of browser and operating system, Internet Service Provider, Internet protocol address, access times, and referring website addresses. We may monitor, use, and share such data to measure the Site’s performance, activity, and improve the Site’s design and functionality. As with many Internet sites, we may use “cookies” or “web beacons” to, among other things, enhance the functionality of the Site and to make transactions and other activities through the Site more convenient and efficient for visitors. A “cookie” is a file stored locally on a user’s computer. Most Internet browsers include preference settings that allow users to be notified and control whether cookies are transferred to their computers.

_Age Restrictions._  Living Essentials does not knowingly market to, solicit or collect data from persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, we ask that you do not to use this Site. While we cannot take any special action to learn your age, if we learn that you are under 18 years of age, we will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you. If you believe your minor-child has provided personally identifiable information to us, please contact us so we can allow you the opportunity to review and delete such information.

_WHEN AND WITH WHOM WE MAY SHARE YOUR INFORMATION_

_Use of Information Collected._  Living Essentials will share your personal information with third-party companies, if necessary, for purposes such as responding to your inquires, providing you the requested services, sending you newsletters, or other business purposes. To the extent Living Essentials hires other companies to provide limited services on its behalf, we will only provide those companies with the information that they need to provide us with such services.

_Third Party Advertising Vendors._ Living Essentials and the Site may use third-party advertising companies (such as Google, Twitter and Facebook) that employ the use of pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs, advertising cookies or other similar technology to help with our online and email advertising campaigns. Living Essentials uses these third party services to deliver targeted ads to you on our Site and across the web on your devices. To learn more about how Google uses cookies in advertising, you can visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy located [HERE](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You can opt out of receiving interest-based Google ads, or customize the ads Google shows you, by clicking [HERE](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout). Likewise, if you elect to register to receive email newsletters Living Essentials will not only use your email for newsletters but it will also be shared with third-party vendors (such as Facebook, Google, and Twitter) to serve targeted ads to you on their respective platforms and across the web. You can learn more about Twitter’s interest-based advertising or opt-out through Twitter [HERE](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405). In addition to the platform specific opt outs you can opt out directly with Living Essentials as detailed in the Opt-Out Choices section below.

_Sale or Transfer._  In the event of the sale of Living Essentials, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, Site or operations, Living Essentials may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with such transaction. In the event of such a transfer, Living Essentials will notify you via email or by posting a prominent notice on our Site for 30 days of any such change in ownership of Living Essentials resulting in a change of control of your personal information.

_Disclosure pursuant to law._  We will also disclose your personal information, without notice, when required to do so to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Living Essentials or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Living Essentials; and, (c) protect the personal safety of users of Living Essentials, its websites, or the public.

_Your Consent to Share._  By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information and the collection and processing of such personal information in the United States. Your personal information will be stored and processed on computers in the United States. The laws on holding personal information in the United States may vary and be less stringent than laws of your state. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential, and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used in this manner, do not register with or use the Site.

_ONLINE TRACKING_  
At this time, this Site does not support Do-Not-Track signals.

_OPT-OUT CHOICES_  
To “opt-out” of (1) any consents previously given to us, (2) receiving communications from us, or (3) having personal information disclosed to third parties, send an e-mail to [opt-out@fivehour.com](mailto:opt-out@fivehour.com). Notwithstanding this right to request to cease receiving communications from us and to have us not share personal information with third parties, we retain the right to collect, maintain and process information provided by and collected about you on and through the Site, and disclose such information to comply with its reasonable business and legal obligations.

_ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION_  
To the extent that you may provide personal information to us on or through the Site, we will allow reasonable access to, and review of, such information, where such information is readily available, upon proper verification and authentication of the person (author) seeking such access and review. You may request review and revisions to your personal information through the [opt-out@fivehour.com](mailto:opt-out@fivehour.com) email address. After receipt of verification, we will change or delete your personal information at your request.

_CONSENT TO PROCESSING_  
By using or providing information to the Site, you understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, processing, sharing, and use of such information in the United States for the purposes set forth in this Policy.

_SECURITY_  
Due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot and do not guarantee that communications with the Site will be free from unauthorized access.

_JOB APPLICANTS_  
Living Essentials only collects the personal information that you voluntarily provide, which may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, employment history, education history, expected income, eligibility to work in the U.S., and any other information you share. We will use that information for the purpose for which such information was provided. We do not request, nor should you provide, sensitive data such as your social security number, driver’s license number, bank account information, credit card information, passwords, or date of birth. Your online application, resume, and/or cover letter may be retained for future reference, or as required by law. We may disclose your application data to third party service providers who perform services for or on behalf of Living Essentials.

_CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY_  
Living Essentials reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use of this Website after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms. Periodically check these terms for revisions.

_Contact Information_  
If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using the Site, contact Living Essentials by email at [opt-out@fivehour.com](mailto:opt-out@fivehour.com), or by mail at:

Living Essentials, LLC  
38955 Hills Tech Drive  
Farmington Hills, MI 48831
